[Brother] Uh. our info is limited.
these guys aren't in our database.
All we really know is that they came
from Guangzhou. China.
I'm still investigating
to get the exact details.
How close are we on the server?
I still got. uh. two-thirds or more?
And the shopping mall migration?
Seventy percent.
It's 'cause we're only working nights.
We have to avoid any tracking by Babylon.
I have to go get Jian myself.
Those bastards are gonna
go after her quickly.
What's that?
I think they already found us.
[engines rumbling]
[♪ soft tense music playing]
[tires screech]
[beeps. whirs]
[drone whirring]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Can't get a clear shot.
Container's in the way.
[J] As expected.
Hold your positions.
We're going in.
[in Japanese] Listen carefully.
Put your personal grudge aside.
Jeong Jinman has
to be captured alive. Translate.
[sighs]
[in English] Jeong Jinman needs
to be captured alive. sir.
He has to be alive.
[sighs]
[in Korean] Just don't get in my way.
You'll die first. Translate.
[in English] Ah. shit.
[Marco. in Japanese] Uh… what he said was…
Ah. die first?
[in English] I didn't get the last part.
[in Japanese] What?
That… one-eyed bastard…
[door slides open]
[sighs]
[♪ soft tense music playing]
[in English]
Appreciate you working so late.
[door closes]
We can begin now.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 04
RAID
[Jin] Understood.
I will retrieve the asset
and put things back in order.
[♪ upbeat music playing over speakers]
[J sighs]
[J] Who is it?
Who could make the great Kusanagi act
so submissively. huh?
[soft exhale]
[Jin sighs]
I can keep on climbing higher and higher.
but there's always another level.
[chuckles softly]
Don't you miss fieldwork?
Not at all.
The smell of blood…
[gags]
…and gunpowder just stays in your nose.
Ugh.
I'd rather be a knight than a pawn anyway.
Or even better. I could be the one
who designs the board in the first place.
[J scoffs]
As for capturing Jeong Jinman.
you need to be the one to do it.
I like the sound of that.
And Q?
Q will…
[sighs]
…get rattled.
I need the one who leads this team
to be someone cold.
[scoffs]
Hmm…
Women's intuition.
[♪ tense music playing]
[drone whirring]
[metallic clanking]
[gunfire]
[electric crackling]
[gunshots]
[air hissing]
[mercenary] Smoke!
[J] Don't panic. Hold your positions.
-[gunfire]
-[mercenary grunts]
[loud thud]
[drone whirring]
[Jin] He's the most skilled agent
in your team.
Don't you think it's long overdue
for J to lead a unit?
I don't think it's combat skills
that determines a good leader.
If the target's Jeong Jinman.
I think it does.
That's not it.
I'm talking about Bale.
[blows raspberry]
[laughs]
Bale's just a hunting dog at this point.
If you take him off his leash.
he'll find Jinman for us.
We should be using that.
[♪ tense music playing]
[sighs]
[soft exhale]
[♪ tense music continues]
Working with Bale to capture Jinman
was actually J's choice as team leader.
[Jin] You can't keep coddling him forever
because he's your little brother.
J has the skills he needs.
Branch Chief…
are you and my brother
still seeing each other?
[metallic clanking]
[whirring]
Heavy radio signal detected.
Remove it.
[Q] If you really cared about Jun…
why stick him with a time bomb like Bale…
and send him after Jeong Jinman?
If you're afraid of things like that.
you're in the wrong line of work entirely.
You should try going back
to being yakuza again.
Or open a bar in Dotonbori
and leave the dangerous missions to us.
[whirring]
[clanks]
[metallic clanking]
[in Korean] Hey. Japanese.
-[in English] It's a trap.
-What?
[in Korean] If they hid the server
in a place like this.
wouldn't it mean they're prepared
to bolt at any moment?
What are you doing?
Translate it.
[in Japanese] If they hid the server
in a place like this.
wouldn't it mean they're prepared
to bolt at any moment?
That's what he's said.
[in English] Bravo. Tango.
find dead ends of containers
that can be connected
to the current Alpha position.
and identify all trucks. cranes.
and modes of transportation
within a 100-meter radius.
[mercenary] Possible ambush on Tango.
[Jin] J. forget about Tango.
[in Japanese]
Hey. didn't you say it was a trap?
What are you doing? Translate it.
[in Korean]
Hey. didn't you say it was a trap?
If it's a trap. we don't go in?
Are you scared?
[in English] Are you scared?
[J sighs]
[♪ tense music playing]
That's right. the enemy of my enemy
should be my friend.
-[whirring]
-[metal cutting screeching]
[whirring continues]
[metal cutting screeching continues]
[grunts]
[fighting grunts]
After you.
[clanking]
Grenade!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[explosion]
[both groaning]
[Bale coughs. groans]
[J] Marco. Marco!
[grunting]
[J pants]
[Marco] I'm okay.
[Marco breathing heavily]
[labored breaths]
I'll be right back.
Jinman's here. that slick fuck.
Bravo. current location?
-[static crackling]
-[indistinct radio chatter]
After you.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
It's a trap.
[gunshots]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[sighs]
[in Japanese] That hurts!
[grunts]
[pants]
Shit.
[fighting grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Long time. no see.
Jeong Jinman.
[chuckles]
[in Japanese]
I'm just sorry we have to meet like this.
[in English] J. don't forget.
We need Jeong Jinman alive.
[fighting grunts]
-[grunts]
-[Jinman breathes heavily]
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
[gunshots]
What the hell's that moron doing?
[Bale grunts]
I told you we have to capture him alive!
-[groans]
-[grunts]
-[Bale breathing heavily]
-[J gurgling]
[choking. gurgling]
[J gurgling continues]
[choking]
I thought I made it clear to you.
If you get in my way. you'll die first.
[choking]
-[angry grunt]
-[groans]
[J wheezes]
[choking]
[sighs]
Shit.
[Jin sighs]
Ugh…
[sighs]
Move it.
[♪ light action music playing]
Shit.
[groaning]
[drone whirs]
Look! Over there!
[rapid gunfire]
[strained grunting]
[grunts. pants]
[gunshots]
Snipers. what are you doing?
Hurry up and stop that truck.
Move to ten o'clock now!
[low mechanical rumbling]
[heavy thudding]
[Brother cries out]
[Brother breathing heavily]
[Cheolseung]
We're out of time. let's haul ass!
[engine starts rumbling]
You always did have something up
your sleeve. Jinman.
[clicks]
Always so petty.
-[fighting grunts]
-[gunshots]
[grunts]
[Jinman panting]
[fighting grunts]
[yells]
[♪ soft tense music playing]
[Brother groans]
[engine rumbling]
Just ram through it!
Hold on to something!
[loud crashing]
[both grunt]
[Jinman breathing heavily]
[fighting grunts]
[Jinman yells in pain]
-[Jinman grunts]
-[yells out in pain]
[growling. grunting]
[strained grunting]
-[Jinman grunts]
-[breathing heavily]
[fighting grunts]
[ragged breathing]
-[Jinman grunts]
-[pained groan]
[loud thud]
[ragged breathing]
[Bale gasps. pants]
[Bale breathes heavily]
[exhales]
[Bale] All these clever little tricks
are only gonna blow up in your face.
[exhales]
-[gasps]
-[beeps]
[explosion]
[Bale wheezing]
[breathing softly]
Jeong Jinman. I'll see you in hell--
[gunshots]
[♪ dark upbeat music playing]
[gun clicks]
[sighs]
[Jin] Tell me.
are we being recorded
in the command center?
No. ma'am.
We don't record
unofficial internal operations.
[sighs quietly]
Good work. everybody.
You can all go home.
Q's operation is in a few hours.
What's our angle here?
Hmm…
I'll figure something out.
[sighs] I'm starving.
Can you handle it?
[♪ soft tense music playing]
[guard sighs deeply]
[engine idling]
[sighs]
[beeps]
Can I get room service?
Even though Bale's a psycho.
how could he kill his own team like that?
Dying like a dog as soon
as you leave Japan…
I heard that J was Q's younger brother.
[sighs]
[♪ soft tense music playing]
[engine rumbling]
[tires squeal]
[fighting grunts]
[J in Japanese] That hurts!
[Jinman pants]
[grunts. pants]
[phone buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
-Yeah?
-[K] Everything is set.
But there are two employees
from another department
and the bus driver on board.
[gasps]
I think that…
looks more natural. don't you think?
[engine rumbling]
[explosion]
[Jin] Whoo! [chuckles]
Good job. K.
[♪ tense music playing]
You understand?
Jeong Jinman was the one who killed J.
Bale didn't do it.
We have to make sure
that Q never discovers the truth
under any circumstances.
This… stays between us.
[♪ tense music continues]
[crickets chirping]
[driver] Fortunately.
the residents had all left the island.
Your friend Miss Arin rushed to Seoul
because of her uncle's sudden passing.
And it looks like she won't be able
to come back.
We'll make it
so nothing happened here tonight.
So. as long as you keep quiet.
that's the end of it.
You'll be free to return
to your normal life.
However.
once Miss Jian leaves here.
you'll be strangers from that moment on.
Any contact is forbidden.
Hey. I don't think that's necess…
That's going too far.
Woojin…
[gasps]
[Woojin breathes shakily]
[driver] If you need help.
you can contact me at this number.
CO.. Ltd. JAEWON CLEANING
Team Leader Kim Jaewon
[door slides open. shut]
[breathes shakily]
[Woojin] Arin…
No.
Your real name is…
Jian. isn't it?
[breathes shakily]
I don't think
I'll be any help cleaning here.
Let me know when it's all done.
I'll be at the house.
Woojin. wait.
[♪ soft piano music playing]
[door slides open]
[door slides shut]
-[crickets chirping]
-[♪ soft piano music continues]
[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
Do you think it's okay to let him leave.
just like that?
There are traces of him
having accessed the app data.
When you catch up. what are you gonna say?
[Minhye] That boy Woojin…
do you like him?
Stay level-headed.
You remember Bae Jeongmin. right?
-We don't know who'll come looking and--
-[Jian] Unni…
I'm really hungry.
Why don't we eat something?
We got some mumallaengi.
Auntie Soonae grows the radishes.
dries and seasons them herself.
It's so good.
And these are bangiip muchin and myeolchi
that Auntie Pilsun made.
And this one…
[chuckles]
Auntie Jeomrye. she found out
I liked sausage and stir-fried vegetables.
so she made this for me.
Ah… [gasps softly]
Meongge-jeot…
Auntie Jeomrye's specialty.
Jian.
we don't have time to be doing this.
[soft thud]
This stuff…
I've never…
[inhales deeply]
I never got to just be like this
with Uncle.
[cries softly]
After getting here…
living a normal life like everyone else.
it was just really nice.
Having someone there for me…
and me being there for them too.
Laughing together.
making meals.
just talking…
normal.
A normal life. you know?
[sighs heavily]
[cries] Living a normal life
like everyone else gets to.
[cries. exhales]
[inhales]
Until yesterday. I really…
[sighs]
…really believed
I could keep going like this.
Look. your uncle really tried.
He did everything he could for you. Jian.
I know he did. I know that.
[cries]
[sniffles]
[inhales]
I found a way here
to live life on my own terms.
It's better than that cage he kept me in
'cause it was dangerous.
And that was his past catching up to us.
It had nothing at all to do with me.
[inhales]
Even still…
if you were to stay here.
Woojin and everyone around you
will all be in danger.
[breathes shakily]
I know that.
[breathes deeply]
[sighs. sniffles]
I'll go back to my uncle. I just…
[sighs]
Could we just…
have one moment?
[inhales]
Can we have one more meal
as normal people first?
[Woojin sighs]
[glass shattering]
[♪ action tense music playing]
[drone whirring]
[♪ action tense music continues]
WOOJIN
[phone buzzing]
[panting]
[engines rumbling]
[engine starts. revs]
[engine revving]
Team Leader. she isn't alone.
How should we handle this?
You can eliminate anyone
who gets in your way.
Just get her.
[suppressed gunshot]
-[whirring]
-[rattling]
[suppressed gunshots]
[engines rumbling]
[gasping]
[Minhye] And for our extraction?
[Jaewon] We can transport you on our ship.
[clanks]
[Woojin] This is bad.
You have to go now!
[engines rumbling]
Woojin. is there another way to the docks?
On the back side of the island.
there's a way there.
Listen carefully.
I'll stay and stall them as long as I can.
Head to the docks with Woojin.
Once you get down there.
find the boat called the JW.
Director Kim. give them cover.
Right. I'm on it.
[engines rumbling]
-[gun clicks]
-[sighs]
Unni.
[in English] I'll be fine.
Listen. your unni will never die.
[♪ action tense music playing]
[engine rumbling]
They're coming!
[rapid gunfire]
[breathes sharply]
[panting]
[drone whirring]
[gunshots]
[Jaewon yells]
[engines revving]
[groans]
[explosion]
[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[engine rumbling]
Team Leader. there's a four-wheeler
headed towards the docks.
It looks like Jeong Jian.
Bravo. start making your way in.
Let's roll out.
[engines rumbling]
[explosion]
[thuds]
[♪ low suspenseful music playing]
[rapid gunfire]
[gunfire]
[Minhye clicks tongue]
[strained grunting]
[grunts]
[pants]
[groaning in pain]
Are you all right?
[sighs]
-[sighs softly]
-[gun clicks]
We have to hurry and catch up to Jian.
[♪ tense music playing]
-Woojin!
-[gasps]
-[drone whirring]
-[engines rumbling]
-[loud blast]
-[yelps]
[engine revs]
[♪ muffled tense music playing]
[breathing deeply]
[Jian inhales deeply]
[gunfire]
[loud blast]
[gasps]
[drone whirring]
[grunts]
[gunfire]
Arin. hold on to me!
[♪ tense music continues]
[tires screech]
[engines rumbling]
[brakes grinding]
[tires screech]
[♪ tense music continues]
-[tires screech]
-[groans]
-[Woojin exclaims]
-[Jian grunts]
-[tires screech]
-[brakes grinding]
[moans. grunts]
-[Woojin] Arin…
-[grunts]
[breathing raggedly]
Arin. get up.
[Jian grunts]
[Q] Jeong Jian…
[Jian grunts raggedly]
Wait. is that your boat over there?
[Jian breathes shakily]
-[explosion]
-[both gasp]
[pants. gasps]
[inhales sharply] You can't!
[breathing heavily]
Shit.
[Q] This is your last chance.
[Jian breathing heavily]
If you don't come with me. your boyfriend
will also die just like that.
-[Jian breathing shakily]
-[chuckles softly]
[engine revving]
[♪ action tense music playing]
[engine revs]
[tires screeching]
-[tires screech]
-[engine revs]
[grunts softly]
-[gunfire]
-[grunts]
[strained grunt]
[rapid gunfire]
[breathing heavily]
Hey. my boat's right there.
[Jian grunts]
[Jian breathing heavily]
[engine rumbling]
[panting]
[gasps awake]
-[tires screech]
-[engine revving]
[♪ dark tense music playing]
[engine revving]
[yells]
[water splashes]
[panting]
You're her. huh?
So Minhye.
[♪ dark tense music continues]
[both grunting]
[grunts]
[fierce grunt]
[both grunt]
[yells]
[pants]
[breathes heavily]
[both grunt]
Woojin. hard left now!
[rattling]
[Q pants]
[engine rumbling]
[Woojin grunts]
[Q panting]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Seal it off.
[whooshes]
[Woojin breathing shakily]
[breathing shakily continues]
[Jian sighs. sniffles]
I'm sorry. Woojin.
[thuds]
[Woojin] I'm doing fine.
Look. I'm still in one piece.
So don't worry.
[Jian crying]
Hey. don't say you forgot.
-do you remember my promise?
-[crying]
[Woojin] In Hanam-do.
I won't let anyone
touch even a hair on your head.
[crying softly]
[♪ soft music playing]
I won't let them get the chance.
[sniffles]
You're right.
They won't have a chance in hell.
[exhales softly]
[♪ tense music playing]
Jian. get down!
-[rapid beeping]
-[gunshots]
Boom.
[explosion]
Give them a warning shot. to wake them up.
Woojin. drop down!
[rapid gunfire]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
[Woojin breathing heavily]
Woojin. Woojin!
[Jian panting]
It's okay. Just wait a second.
[gunfire]
Jeong Jian!
[Q] I want Jeong Jian brought in alive.
[cries softly]
Jian. hey…
[weakly] Jeong Jian.
[crying]
[Jian breathes shakily]
[cries]
[breathes shakily]
[♪ somber music playing]
That's your name. right?
[inhales sharply]
Jeong Jian?
[crying]
Uh-huh.
[sobbing]
[Jian crying]
Even your name is beautiful. Jian.
-[sniffles. cries]
-I…
-[mumbles]
-[Jian crying]
Hey. didn't I promise you?
Not a single hair.
Not a single hair on your head.
[sobbing]
Let me just say…
thanks for hanging out…
with a hick like me.
[gasps]
[Jian sobbing]
Woojin. hey!
Don't close your eyes!
No! You can't…
[sobbing]
You can't…
[sobbing continues]
[rapid gunfire]
Jeong Jinman!
[inaudible] Jeong Jinman!
[♪ somber music continues]
[rapid gunfire]
[explosion]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[rapid gunfire]
[explosion]
[breathes shakily]
[helicopter whirring overhead]
[exhales in relief]
[crying]
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
[♪ closing theme music playing]
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today